<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Umair Durrani</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Umair Durrani</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Everything in Windows</title>
      <link>/2018/02/27/search-everything-in-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/27/search-everything-in-windows/</guid>
      <description>I just watched a YouTube video by Hadley Wickham (author of several R packages) who talked about project workflow. He told about using a search and launch application called alfred. Since alfred is only available on Mac, I searched alternatives for Windows. The one I liked among many is Everything. It makes Windows search so fast. Following is a little demonstration by someone on YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>/2018/02/18/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/18/first-post/</guid>
      <description>My first post via blogdown!
Yay!
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides from graduate seminar on Driving Control Strategies in Car-following</title>
      <link>/2018/02/18/slides-from-graduate-seminar-on-driving-control-strategies-in-car-following/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/18/slides-from-graduate-seminar-on-driving-control-strategies-in-car-following/</guid>
      <description>This is an embedded Microsoft Office presentation, powered by Office Online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Umair Durrani and I have over 5 years of experience in traffic data analysis and driver behavior. I use tools such as PTV VISSIM, R, RStudio, Python and Excel for analysis and reporting the insights gained about road transportation.
My passion is to effectively use data to improve safety and traffic flow on transportation systems. For this purpose, I don&amp;rsquo;t merely rely on black box tools to predict traffic flow but also try to disseminate the knowledge from data to understand the underlying causes e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>